var list = [{
  question: 'What do you call an artificial or natural body that revolves around a larger body?',
  choiceA: 'moon',
  choiceB: 'asteroid',
  choiceC: 'satellite',
  choiceD: 'planet',
  answer: this.choiceC
},
{
  question: 'A common method for scientists to measure distances within the solar system is to use...',
  choiceA: 'the Speed of Sound',
  choiceB: 'the Imperial System',
  choiceC: 'the Speed of Time',
  choiceD: 'the Astronomical Unit',
  answer: this.choiceD
},
{
  question: 'What were smaller moons usually before they became moons?',
  choiceA: 'comets',
  choiceB: 'meteoroids',
  choiceC: 'dwarf planets',
  choiceD: 'asteroids',
  answer: this.choiceD
},
{
  question: 'How do the inner planets differ from the outer planets?',
  choiceA: 'They are made of lighter elements.',
  choiceB: 'They do not have any moons.',
  choiceC: 'They are more likely to have geologic activity.',
  choiceD: 'They are smaller and fluffier',
  answer: this.choiceC
},
{
  question: 'How could a rock from our moon tell us the age of our Solar System?',
  choiceA: 'The rock has not changed since the moon first formed.',
  choiceB: 'It canâ€™t; erosion, weathering, and tectonic activity will have changed it.',
  choiceC: 'Space is really clean so the rock would be too.',
  choiceD: 'It\'s an inanimate object, it\'s not telling us anything!',
  answer: this.choiceA
},
{
  question: 'What is one factor that makes life possible on Earth?',
  choiceA: 'our distance from the sun',
  choiceB: 'liquid water on its surface',
  choiceC: 'a protective atmosphere that also regulates our climate',
  choiceD: 'all of the above',
  answer: this.choiceD
},
{
  question: 'Why is it useful to study the smaller objects of the solar system?',
  choiceA: 'Scientists can use them to study the early solar system.',
  choiceB: 'Scientists can use them to make new and stronger materials for building.',
  choiceC: 'Studying them will tell us what kind of force field to build',
  choiceD: 'So we can determine which ones can be mined for raw materials',
  answer: this.choiceA
},
{
  question: 'Which of the following is a characteristic of the outer planets?',
  choiceA: 'dense and rocky',
  choiceB: 'they have many moons',
  choiceC: 'lots of geologic activity',
  choiceD: 'thin to no atmospheres',
  answer: this.choiceB
},
{
  question: 'Which set of planets all have rings around them?',
  choiceA: 'Inner Planets',
  choiceB: 'Outer Planets',
  choiceC: 'Terrestrial Planets',
  choiceD: 'None of the above',
  answer: this.choiceB
},
{
  question: 'Which of the following are NOT objects we would find in space, in our solar system?',
  choiceA: 'asteroids',
  choiceB: 'rings',
  choiceC: 'meteorites',
  choiceD: 'comets',
  answer: this.choiceC
},];
